<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Docker and System Docker on BurmillaOS</title><link>https://burmillaos.org/docs/configuration/docker/</link><description>Recent content in Docker and System Docker on BurmillaOS</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://burmillaos.org/docs/configuration/docker/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Images prefix</title><link>https://burmillaos.org/docs/configuration/docker/images-prefix/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://burmillaos.org/docs/configuration/docker/images-prefix/</guid><description>Images prefix # When you have built your own docker registries, and have cached the burmilla/os and other os-services images, something like a normal docker pull burmilla/os can be cached as docker pull dockerhub.mycompanyname.com/docker.io/burmilla/os.
However, you need a way to inject a prefix into BurmillaOS for installation or service pulls. BurmillaOS supports a global prefix you can add to force ROS to always use your mirror.
You can config a global image prefix:</description></item><item><title>Private Registries</title><link>https://burmillaos.org/docs/configuration/docker/private-registries/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://burmillaos.org/docs/configuration/docker/private-registries/</guid><description>Private Registries # When launching services through a cloud-config, it is sometimes necessary to pull a private image from DockerHub or from a private registry. Authentication for these can be embedded in your cloud-config.
For example, to add authentication for DockerHub:
#cloud-config rancher: registry_auths: https://index.docker.io/v1/: auth: dXNlcm5hbWU6cGFzc3dvcmQ= The auth key is generated by base64 encoding a string of the form username:password. The docker login command can be used to generate an auth key.</description></item><item><title>Setting up Docker TLS</title><link>https://burmillaos.org/docs/configuration/docker/setting-up-docker-tls/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://burmillaos.org/docs/configuration/docker/setting-up-docker-tls/</guid><description>Setting up Docker TLS # ros tls generate is used to generate both the client and server TLS certificates for Docker.
Remember, all ros commands need to be used with sudo or as a root user.
End to end example # Enable TLS for Docker and Generate Server Certificate # To have docker secured by TLS you need to set rancher.docker.tls to true, and generate a set of server and client keys and certificates:</description></item><item><title>Switching Docker Versions</title><link>https://burmillaos.org/docs/configuration/docker/switching-docker-versions/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://burmillaos.org/docs/configuration/docker/switching-docker-versions/</guid><description>Switching Docker Versions # The version of User Docker used in BurmillaOS can be configured using a cloud-config file or by using the ros engine command.
Note: There are known issues in Docker when switching between versions. For production systems, we recommend setting the Docker engine only once using a cloud-config.
Available Docker engines # The ros engine list command can be used to show which Docker engines are available to switch to.</description></item></channel></rss>