<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>BurmillaOS</title><link>https://burmillaos.org/docs/configuration/base/</link><description>Recent content on BurmillaOS</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://burmillaos.org/docs/configuration/base/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Consoles</title><link>https://burmillaos.org/docs/configuration/base/switching-consoles/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://burmillaos.org/docs/configuration/base/switching-consoles/</guid><description>Consoles # When booting from the ISO, BurmillaOS starts with the default console, which is based on busybox.
You can select which console you want BurmillaOS to start with using the cloud-config.
Enabling Consoles using Cloud-Config # When launching BurmillaOS with a cloud-config file, you can select which console you want to use.
Currently, the list of available consoles are:
default (debian) Here is an example cloud-config file that can be used to enable the debian console.</description></item><item><title>Date and time zone</title><link>https://burmillaos.org/docs/configuration/base/date-and-timezone/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://burmillaos.org/docs/configuration/base/date-and-timezone/</guid><description>Date and time zone # Host system # The default console keeps time in the Coordinated Universal Time (UTC) zone and synchronizes clocks with the Network Time Protocol (NTP). The Network Time Protocol daemon (ntpd) is an operating system program that maintains the system time in synchronization with time servers using the NTP.
Changing the timezone in the default console can be for example done using a system-wide environment variable /etc/environment</description></item><item><title>Setting the Hostname</title><link>https://burmillaos.org/docs/configuration/base/hostname/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://burmillaos.org/docs/configuration/base/hostname/</guid><description>Setting the Hostname # You can set the hostname of the host using cloud-config. The example below shows how to configure it.
#cloud-config hostname: myhost</description></item><item><title>SSH Settings</title><link>https://burmillaos.org/docs/configuration/base/ssh-keys/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://burmillaos.org/docs/configuration/base/ssh-keys/</guid><description>SSH Settings # BurmillaOS supports adding SSH keys through the cloud-config file. Within the cloud-config file, you simply add the ssh keys within the ssh_authorized_keys key.
#cloud-config ssh_authorized_keys: - ssh-rsa AAA...ZZZ example1@burmilla - ssh-rsa BBB...ZZZ example2@burmilla When we pass the cloud-config file during the ros install command, it will allow these ssh keys to be associated with the burmilla user. You can ssh into BurmillaOS using the key.
$ ssh -i /path/to/private/key burmilla@&amp;lt;ip-address&amp;gt; Please note that OpenSSH 7.</description></item><item><title>Users</title><link>https://burmillaos.org/docs/configuration/base/users/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://burmillaos.org/docs/configuration/base/users/</guid><description>Users # Currently, we don&amp;rsquo;t support adding other users besides burmilla.
You can add users in the console container, but these users will only exist as long as the console container exists. It only makes sense to add users in a persistent consoles.
If you want the console user to be able to ssh into BurmillaOS, you need to add them to the docker group.</description></item></channel></rss>