<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>BurmillaOS</title><link>https://burmillaos.org/docs/storage/</link><description>Recent content on BurmillaOS</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://burmillaos.org/docs/storage/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title/><link>https://burmillaos.org/docs/storage/custom-partition-layout/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://burmillaos.org/docs/storage/custom-partition-layout/</guid><description>How to custom partition layout # When users use the default ros install, ROS will automatically create one partition on the root disk. It will be the only partition with the label BURMILLA_STATE. But sometimes users want to be able to customize the root disk partition to isolate the data.
The following defaults to MBR mode, GPT mode has not been tested.
Partions # BURMILLA_STATE # As mentioned above, the default mode is that ROS will automatically create one partition with the label BURMILLA_STATE.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://burmillaos.org/docs/storage/additional-mounts/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://burmillaos.org/docs/storage/additional-mounts/</guid><description>Additional Mounts # Additional mounts can be specified as part of your cloud-config. These mounts are applied within the console container. Here&amp;rsquo;s a simple example that mounts /dev/vdb to /mnt/s.
#cloud-config mounts: - [&amp;#34;/dev/vdb&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;/mnt/s&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;ext4&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;&amp;#34;] Important: Be aware, the 4th parameter is mandatory and cannot be omitted (server crashes). It also yet cannot be defaults
As you will use the ros cli most probably, it would look like this:</description></item><item><title/><link>https://burmillaos.org/docs/storage/state-partition/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://burmillaos.org/docs/storage/state-partition/</guid><description>Persistent State Partition # BurmillaOS will store its state in a single partition specified by the dev field. The field can be a device such as /dev/sda1 or a logical name such LABEL=state or UUID=123124. The default value is LABEL=BURMILLA_STATE. The file system type of that partition can be set to auto or a specific file system type such as ext4.
#cloud-config rancher: state: fstype: auto dev: LABEL=BURMILLA_STATE For other labels such as BURMILLA_BOOT and BURMILLA_OEM and BURMILLA_SWAP, please refer to Custom partition layout.</description></item><item><title>Using ZFS</title><link>https://burmillaos.org/docs/storage/using-zfs/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://burmillaos.org/docs/storage/using-zfs/</guid><description>Using ZFS # Installing the ZFS service # The zfs service will install the kernel-headers for your kernel (if you build your own kernel, you&amp;rsquo;ll need to replicate this service), and then download the ZFS on Linux source, and build and install it. Then it will build a zfs-tools image that will be used to give you access to the zfs tools.
The only restriction is that you must mount your zpool into /mnt, as this is the only shared mount directory that will be accessible throughout the system-docker managed containers (including the console).</description></item></channel></rss>