<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>BurmillaOS</title><link>https://burmillaos.org/docs/installation/custom-builds/</link><description>Recent content on BurmillaOS</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://burmillaos.org/docs/installation/custom-builds/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title/><link>https://burmillaos.org/docs/installation/custom-builds/custom-console/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://burmillaos.org/docs/installation/custom-builds/custom-console/</guid><description>Custom Console # When booting from the ISO, BurmillaOS starts with the default console, which is based on busybox.
You can select which console you want BurmillaOS to start with using the cloud-config.
Enabling Consoles using Cloud-Config # When launching BurmillaOS with a cloud-config file, you can select which console you want to use.
Currently, the list of available consoles are:
default Here is an example cloud-config file that can be used to enable the debian console.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://burmillaos.org/docs/installation/custom-builds/custom-kernels/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://burmillaos.org/docs/installation/custom-builds/custom-kernels/</guid><description>Custom Kernels # Kernel version in BurmillaOS # BurmillaOS basically uses the standard Linux kernel, but we maintain a kernel config ourselves. Due to various feature support and security fixes, we are constantly updating the kernel version.
BurmillaOS Kernel =v2.0.x 5.9.x =v1.9.x 4.14.x Building and Packaging a Kernel to be used in BurmillaOS # We build the kernel for BurmillaOS at the os-kernel repository.</description></item><item><title>Custom BurmillaOS ISO</title><link>https://burmillaos.org/docs/installation/custom-builds/custom-burmillaos-iso/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://burmillaos.org/docs/installation/custom-builds/custom-burmillaos-iso/</guid><description>Custom BurmillaOS ISO # It&amp;rsquo;s easy to build your own BurmillaOS ISO.
Create a clone of the main BurmillaOS repository to your local machine with a git clone.
$ git clone https://github.com/burmilla/os.git In the root of the repository, the &amp;ldquo;General Configuration&amp;rdquo; section of Dockerfile.dapper can be updated to use custom kernels. After you&amp;rsquo;ve saved your edits, run make in the root directory. After the build has completed, a ./dist/artifacts directory will be created with the custom built BurmillaOS release files.</description></item></channel></rss>