<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>BurmillaOS</title><link>https://burmillaos.org/docs/installation/cloud/</link><description>Recent content on BurmillaOS</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://burmillaos.org/docs/installation/cloud/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Amazon EC2</title><link>https://burmillaos.org/docs/installation/cloud/aws-ec2/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://burmillaos.org/docs/installation/cloud/aws-ec2/</guid><description>Amazon EC2 # BurmillaOS is available as an Amazon Web Services AMI, and can be easily run on EC2. You can launch BurmillaOS either using the AWS Command Line Interface (CLI) or using the AWS console.
Launching BurmillaOS through the AWS CLI # If you haven&amp;rsquo;t installed the AWS CLI, follow the instructions on the AWS CLI page to install the CLI and configure access key and secret keys.</description></item><item><title>Amazon ECS</title><link>https://burmillaos.org/docs/installation/cloud/amazon-ecs/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://burmillaos.org/docs/installation/cloud/amazon-ecs/</guid><description>Amazon ECS (EC2 Container Service) # Amazon ECS is supported, which allows BurmillaOS EC2 instances to join your cluster.
Pre-Requisites # Prior to launching BurmillaOS EC2 instances, the ECS Container Instance IAM Role will need to have been created. This ecsInstanceRole will need to be used when launching EC2 instances. If you have been using ECS, you created this role if you followed the ECS &amp;ldquo;Get Started&amp;rdquo; interactive guide.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://burmillaos.org/docs/installation/cloud/aliyun/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://burmillaos.org/docs/installation/cloud/aliyun/</guid><description>Aliyun # Adding the BurmillaOS Image into Aliyun # BurmillaOS is available as an image in Aliyun, and can be easily run in Elastic Compute Service (ECS). Let’s walk through how to upload the ECS image.
Download the most recent BurmillaOS image. The image burmillaos-aliyun.vhd can be found in the release artifacts. Follow Aliyun&amp;rsquo;s instructions on how to upload the image. Before the image can be added, it must be uploaded into an OSS bucket.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://burmillaos.org/docs/installation/cloud/azure/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://burmillaos.org/docs/installation/cloud/azure/</guid><description>Azure # BurmillaOS has been published in Azure Marketplace, you can get it from here.
Launching BurmillaOS through the Azure Portal # Using the new Azure Resource Management portal, click on Marketplace. Search for BurmillaOS. Click on Create.
Follow the steps to create a virtual machine.
In the Basics step, provide a name for the VM, use burmilla as the user name and select the SSH public key option of authenticating.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://burmillaos.org/docs/installation/cloud/digital-ocean/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://burmillaos.org/docs/installation/cloud/digital-ocean/</guid><description>Digital Ocean # BurmillaOS is available in the Digital Ocean portal. BurmillaOS is a member of container distributions and you can find it easily.
Note Deploying to Digital Ocean will incur charges.
To start a BurmillaOS Droplet on Digital Ocean:
In the Digital Ocean portal, go to the project view. Click New Droplet. Click Create Droplet. Click the Container distributions tab. Click BurmillaOS. Choose a plan. Make sure your Droplet has the minimum hardware requirements for BurmillaOS.</description></item><item><title>Google Compute Engine (GCE)</title><link>https://burmillaos.org/docs/installation/cloud/gce/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://burmillaos.org/docs/installation/cloud/gce/</guid><description>Google Compute Engine (GCE) # Note: Due to the maximum transmission unit (MTU) of 1460 bytes on GCE, you will need to configure your network interfaces and both the Docker and System Docker to use a MTU of 1460 bytes or you will encounter weird networking related errors.
Adding the BurmillaOS Image into GCE # BurmillaOS is available as an image in GCE, and can be easily run in Google Compute Engine (GCE).</description></item><item><title>OpenStack</title><link>https://burmillaos.org/docs/installation/cloud/openstack/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://burmillaos.org/docs/installation/cloud/openstack/</guid><description>OpenStack # BurmillaOS releases include an Openstack image that can be found on our releases page. The image format is QCOW3 that is backward compatible with QCOW2.
When launching an instance using the image, you must enable Advanced Options -&amp;gt; Configuration Drive and in order to use a cloud-config file.</description></item><item><title>VMware ESXi</title><link>https://burmillaos.org/docs/installation/cloud/vmware-esxi/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://burmillaos.org/docs/installation/cloud/vmware-esxi/</guid><description>VMware ESXi # BurmillaOS automatically detects that it is running on VMware ESXi, and automatically adds the open-vm-tools service to be downloaded and started, and uses guestinfo keys to set the cloud-init data.
BurmillaOS releases anything required for VMware, which includes initrd, a standard ISO for VMware, a vmdk image, and a specific ISO to be used with Docker Machine. The open-vm-tools is built in to BurmillaOS, there is no need to download it.</description></item></channel></rss>