<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Docs on BurmillaOS</title><link>https://burmillaos.org/docs/</link><description>Recent content in Docs on BurmillaOS</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://burmillaos.org/docs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title/><link>https://burmillaos.org/docs/quick-start-guide/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://burmillaos.org/docs/quick-start-guide/</guid><description>Quick Start # If you have a specific BurmillaOS machine requirements, please check out our guides on running BurmillaOS. With the rest of this guide, we&amp;rsquo;ll start up a BurmillaOS using Docker machine and show you some of what BurmillaOS can do.
Launching BurmillaOS using Docker Machine # Before moving forward, you&amp;rsquo;ll need to have Docker Machine and VirtualBox installed. Once you have VirtualBox and Docker Machine installed, it&amp;rsquo;s just one command to get BurmillaOS running.</description></item><item><title>FAQs</title><link>https://burmillaos.org/docs/faqs/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://burmillaos.org/docs/faqs/</guid><description>FAQs # What is required to run BurmillaOS? # BurmillaOS runs on any laptop, physical, or virtual servers.
What are some commands? # Command Description docker Good old Docker, use that to run stuff. system-docker The Docker instance running the system containers. Must run as root or using sudo ros Control and configure BurmillaOS How can I extend my disk size in Amazon?</description></item><item><title>Releases</title><link>https://burmillaos.org/docs/releases/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://burmillaos.org/docs/releases/</guid><description>Releases # The following is a list of the versions of the operating system in their different branches:
Stable # v2.0.0 | 2024-03-05 Old stable # v1.9.7-rc1 | 2023-02-01 v1.9.6 | 2023-01-02 Testing # Archived # v1.9.5 | 2022-09-15 v1.9.4 | 2022-03-10 v1.9.3 | 2021-10-12 v1.9.2 | 2021-08-04 v1.9.1 | 2021-02-02 v1.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://burmillaos.org/docs/reference/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://burmillaos.org/docs/reference/</guid><description>Reference # ros Commands # Commands / Options Description Example  --version / -v print the version ros -v  --help / -h show help ros -h os operating system upgrade/downgrade see below config configure settings see below console manage which console container is used see below install install BurmillaOS to disk see below engine manage which Docker engine is used see below service see below tls setup tls configuration see below ros os Sub-Commands # Commands / Options Description Example version show the currently installed version ros os version list list the current available versions ros os list  --update / -u update engine cache ros os list --update upgrade upgrade to the latest version ros os upgrade  --image / -i upgrade to a certain image ros os upgrade --image value  --stage / -s only stage the new upgrade, don&amp;rsquo;t apply it ros os upgrade --stage  --force / -f do not prompt for input ros os upgrade --force  --kexec / -k reboot using kexec ros os upgrade --kexec  --no-reboot do not reboot after update ros os upgrade --no-reboot  --append append additional kernel parameters ros os upgrade --append value  --upgrade-console upgrade console even if persistent ros os upgrade --upgrade-console  --debug run installer with debug output ros os upgrade --debug ros config Sub-Commands # Commands / Options Description Example get get value ros config get value set set a value ros config set value images list Docker images for a configuration from a file ros config images  --input / -i file from which to read config ros config images --input value generate generate a configuration file from a template ros config generate merge merge configuration from stdin ros config merge  --input / -i file from which to read ros config merge --input value export export configuration ros config export  --output / -o file to which to save ros config export --output value  --private / -p include the generated private keys ros config export --private  --full / -f export full configuration, including internal and default settings ros config export --full validate validate configuration form stdin ros config validate  --input / -i file from which to read ros config validate --input value syslinux edit Syslinux boot global.</description></item></channel></rss>